Guide to the Jewish Labor Committee Records, Part III WAG.025.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series V: Departments, Chapters, and Divisions, 1940-2009
  - Subseries A: Anti-Discrimination Department, 1943-1969
    - Union of Hebrew Congregations, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 5)
    - United Automobile Workers (UAW), 1960 (Box 333, Folder 6)
    - United Nations, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 7)
    - United Steelworkers, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 8)
    - Urban League of Greater New York, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 9)
    - Voting Discrimination, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 10)
    - Workers Defense League, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 11)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 12)
    - Zimmerman, Charles, 1960 (Box 333, Folder 13)
    - Amalgamated Meat Cutters, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 14)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 15)
    - AFL–CIO, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 16)
    - AFL–CIO: Civil Rights Department, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 17)
    - AFL–CIO: Department of Education, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 18)
    - AFL–CIO: Equal Opportunity for Higher Education Conference, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 19)
    - AFL–CIO: Industrial Union Department, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 20)
    - AFL-CIO: Press Relations, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 21)
    - American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1961 (Box 333, Folder 22)
    - American Federation of Teachers (AFT), 1961 (Box 333, Folder 23)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 24)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 25)
    - American Labor Education Service, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 26)
    - Anti–Defamation League (ADL), 1961 (Box 333, Folder 27)
    - Anti-Defamation League (ADL)/JLC, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 28)
    - Anti-Semitism: General, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 29)
    - Anti-Semitism: Genocide, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 30)
    - Anti-Semitism: Heusinger, Adolf, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 31)
    - Anti-Semitism: Swastika Vandalism, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 32)
    - Anti-Semitism: United States, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 33)
    - Anti-Semitism: United States Racist Publications, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 34)
    - Apprenticeship, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 35)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 36)
    - Black–Jewish Relations, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 37)
    - Black Muslims, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 38)
    - Bright, Leonard, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 39)
    - Canadian Labor Congress, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 40)
    - Children and Prejudice, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 41)
    - Civil Liberties: Supreme Court Decisions, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 42)
    - Civil Rights Committees, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 43)
    - Civil Rights Legislation: Federal, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 44)
    - Civil Rights Legislation: Municipal, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 45)
    - Civil Rights Legislation: State, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 46)
    - Clippings, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 47)
    - Commission on Civil Rights, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 48)
    - Committee on Civil Rights in Manhattan, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 49)
    - Committee on Civil Rights in Metropolitan New York, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 50)
    - Communism, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 51)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Atlanta, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 52)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Birmingham, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 53)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Boston, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 54)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Boston Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 55)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Brooklyn, 1961 (Box 333, Folder 56)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Canada, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 1)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Chicago, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 2-3)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Chicago Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 4)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Cincinnati, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 5)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Detroit, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 6)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Detroit Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 7)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Houston, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 8)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Kansas City, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 9)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Los Angeles, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 10)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Los Angeles Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 11)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Minneapolis, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 12)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Minneapolis Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 13)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Minnesota, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 14)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Philadelphia, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 15-16)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Philadelphia Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 17)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Pittsburgh, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 18)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Saint Louis, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 19)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): San Francisco, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 20-21)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): San Francisco Monthly Reports, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 22)
    - Community Relations Council (CRC): Washington, DC, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 23)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1961 (Box 334, Folder 24)
    - Consultative Conference: Mass Media Committee, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 25)
    - Council of Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 26)
    - Eichmann Trial, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 27-28)
    - Employment: General, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 29-30)
    - Employment: Negroes, 1961 (Box 334, Folder 31)
    - Episcopal Society for Cultural and Racial Unity, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 1)
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission (FEPC), 1961 (Box 335, Folder 2)
    - Field Reports, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 3)
    - Freedom Rides, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 4)
    - Goldberg. J. Arthur, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 5)
    - Hill, Herbert, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 6)
    - Hotel and Restaurant Employees Union (HERE), 1961 (Box 335, Folder 7)
    - Housing: Federal Rulings, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 8)
    - Housing: General, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 9)
    - Housing: JLC, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 10)
    - Housing: Labor, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 11)
    - Housing: NYC, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 12)
    - Housing: NY State, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 13)
    - Housing: Public, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 14)
    - Housing: State Laws, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 15)
    - Housing: Surveys, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 16)
    - Humane Slaughter, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 17)
    - Inter-Group Relations, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 18)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1961 (Box 335, Folder 19)
    - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), 1961 (Box 335, Folder 20)
    - Israel, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 21)
    - JLC, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 22)
    - JLC: National Trade Union Conference on Civil Rights Speeches and Reports, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 23)
    - JLC: "News", 1961 (Box 335, Folder 24)
    - JLC: "News Clips", 1961 (Box 335, Folder 25-26)
    - Jewish Occupational Council, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 27)
    - Jewish War Veterans, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 28)
    - Kessel, George, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 29)
    - Kirschenbanm, Walter, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 30)
    - Labor and Civil Rights, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 31)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Conventions, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 32)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Discrimination in Unions, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 33)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: International Unions, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 34)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Institutes, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 35)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Local Unions, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 36)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Resolutions, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 37)
    - Large City Budgeting Committee, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 38)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 39)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 40)
    - Letter Carriers, National Association of, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 41)
    - Local 1707, CSAE, AFCME, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 42)
    - Mass Media Committee, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 43)
    - Memos to Community Relations Councils, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 44)
    - Memos to Field Staff, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 45-46)
    - Memos: Interoffice, 1961 (Box 335, Folder 47)
    - Muravchik: Trips, Bills, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 1)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1961 (Box 336, Folder 2)
    - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials (NAIRO), 1961 (Box 336, Folder 3)
    - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 4)
    - National Collegiate Debate, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 5)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 6)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC), 1961 (Box 336, Folder 7-8)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Civil Liberties, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 9)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Community Consultation, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 10)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Community Relations Aspects of Developments in the Middle East, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 11)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Work with Education Institutions, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 12)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Executive Committee, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 13)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Immigration Committee, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 14)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Joint Advisory Committee, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 15)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Mass Media Committee, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 16)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Reassessment Committee, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 17)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 18)
    - National Conference of Jewish Communal Service, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 19)
    - National Education Association, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 20)
    - National Sharecroppers Fund: Financial Matters, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 21)
    - National Trade Union Conference, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 22)
    - National Urban League, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 23)
    - Negro American Labor Council, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 24)
    - New York Central Labor Council: Civil Rights Committee, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 25)
    - New York City Commission on Intergroup Relations, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 26)
    - New York City Committee on Jewish Affairs, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 27)
    - New York Panel on Civil Rights, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 28)
    - New York State Attorney Generals Office Correspondence, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 29)
    - New York State Citizens Committee on Farm Labor, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 30)
    - New York State Commission Against Discrimination, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 31)
    - New York State Committee on Discrimination in Housing, 1961 (Box 336, Folder 32)
    - President's Committee on Equal Job Opportunity, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 1)
    - Reich, Sam, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 2)
    - Religion and Labor Foundation, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 3)
    - Remsen, Steve, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 4)
    - Requests for JLC Literature, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 5)
    - Rockwell, George Lincoln: CRC Reports, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 6)
    - Rockwell, George Lincoln: JLC Position, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 7)
    - Rule 22 (Filibuster), 1961 (Box 337, Folder 8)
    - Schools (North): General, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 9)
    - Schools (North): New York, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 10)
    - Schools (South): Economic Effects, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 11)
    - Schools (South): General, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 12)
    - Schools (South): Labor, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 13)
    - Sears Roebuck Boycott Campaign, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 14)
    - South, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 15)
    - Southern Interagency Conference, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 16)
    - Southern Project, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 17)
    - Southern Regional Council, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 18)
    - Student League for Industrial Democracy, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 19)
    - Student Nonviolent Coordinating Committee, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 20)
    - Telegrams, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 21)
    - Textile Workers Union of America, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 22)
    - Tobenkin Memorial Award Committee, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 23)
    - Ultra-Right, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 24)
    - Ultra-Right: Community Relations Councils Reports, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 25)
    - Ultra-Right: Greenwich Conference, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 26)
    - Ultra-Right: John Birch Society, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 27)
    - Ultra-Right: Research Reports, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 28)
    - Ultra-Right: Statements on, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 29)
    - Union of Hebrew Congregations, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 30)
    - United Automobile Workers (UAW), 1961 (Box 337, Folder 31)
    - United Automobile Workers (UAW): Fair Practices Department, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 32)
    - United Nations, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 33)
    - United States Department of Labor, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 34)
    - United Steelworkers, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 35)
    - Urban League of Greater New York, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 36)
    - Voting, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 37)
    - White House Conference on Children and Youth, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 38)
    - Workmen's Circle, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 39)
    - Zimmerman, S. Charles, 1961 (Box 337, Folder 40)
    - Albany, GA, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 41)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America (ACWA), 1962 (Box 337, Folder 42)
    - American Civil Liberties Union, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 43)
    - American Federation of Labor-Congress of Industrial Organizations (AFL-CIO), 1962 (Box 337, Folder 44)
    - AFL-CIO Civil Rights Department, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 45)
    - AFL-CIO: Department of Education, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 46)
    - AFL-CIO: Department of International Affairs, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 47)
    - AFL-CIO: Equal Opportunity for Higher Education Conference, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 48)
    - AFL-CIO Human Rights Committee, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 49)
    - AFL-CIO: Industrial Union Department, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 50)
    - AFL-CIO: Press Releases, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 51)
    - American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), 1962 (Box 337, Folder 52)
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 53)
    - American Jewish Committee, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 54)
    - American Jewish Congress, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 55)
    - American ORT Federations, Inc., 1962 (Box 337, Folder 56)
    - Americans for Democratic Action (ADA), 1962 (Box 337, Folder 57)
    - Anti-Defamation League, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 58)
    - Anti-Semitism: Argentina and Uruguay, 1962 (Box 337, Folder 59)
    - Anti-Semitism: General, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 1)
    - Anti-Semitism: International, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 2)
    - Anti-Semitism: Swastika Vandalism, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 3)
    - Anti-Semitism: United States, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 4)
    - Apprenticeship, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 5-6)
    - Association of Jewish Community Relations Workers, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 7)
    - Barnett Case, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 8)
    - Bershatsky, Harris, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 9)
    - Blacks and Jews, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 10)
    - Black Muslims, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 11)
    - B'nail B'rith Exhibit, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 12)
    - Brotherhood Week, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 13)
    - Bureau Jewish Employment Problems, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 14)
    - Business, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 15)
    - Catholic International Council, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 16)
    - Catholic Press Clippings, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 17)
    - Children and Prejudice, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 18)
    - City Commission on Human Rights, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 19)
    - Civil Liberties: General, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 20)
    - Civil Liberties: Supreme Court Decisions, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 21)
    - Civil Rights Committees, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 22)
    - Civil Rights: General, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 23)
    - Civil Rights Legislation: Federal, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 24)
    - Civil Rights Legislation: State, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 25)
    - Committee on Civil Rights in Metropolitan new York, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 26)
    - Community Relations Council: Boston, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 27)
    - Community Relations Council: Canada, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 28)
    - Community Relations Council: Chicago, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 29)
    - Community Relations Council: Chicago Monthly Report, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 30)
    - Community Relations Council: Cincinnati, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 31)
    - Community Relations Council: Cleveland, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 32)
    - Community Relations Council: Detroit, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 33-34)
    - Community Relations Council: Detroit Monthly Reports, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 35)
    - Community Relations Council: Los Angeles, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 36)
    - Community Relations Council: Los Angeles Monthly Report, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 37)
    - Community Relations Council: Minnesota, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 38)
    - Community Relations Council: Montreal, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 39)
    - Community Relations Council: Pennsylvania, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 40)
    - Community Relations Council: Philadelphia, 1962 (Box 338, Folder 41-42)
    - Community Relations Council: Philadelphia, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 1)
    - Community Relations Council: Philadelphia Monthly Reports, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 2)
    - Community Relations Council: Pittsburgh, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 3)
    - Community Relations Council: Pittsburgh Monthly Reports, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 4)
    - Community Relations Council: San Francisco, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 5)
    - Community Relations Council: San Francisco Monthly Reports, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 6)
    - Community Relations Council: St. Paul, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 7)
    - Community Relations Council: St. Paul Monthly Reports, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 8)
    - Community Relations Council: Syracuse, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 9)
    - Conference for Preservation of Democratic Process, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 10)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE), 1962 (Box 339, Folder 11)
    - Council of Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 12)
    - Employment: General, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 13)
    - Employment: Negroes, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 14)
    - Emancipation Proclamation, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 15)
    - Episcopal Society for Cultural and Racial Unity, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 16)
    - Fair Employment Practices Commission (FEPC), 1962 (Box 339, Folder 17)
    - Feder Case, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 18)
    - Fund for the Republic, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 19)
    - Germany: SPD, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 20)
    - Greater New York Membership Division, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 21)
    - Group Research: Directory of Right-Wing Organizations, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 22-23)
    - Hate Groups, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 24)
    - Hill, Herbert, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 25)
    - Hospital Strike, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 26)
    - Housing: Federal Rulings, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 27)
    - Housing: General, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 28)
    - Housing: JLC, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 29)
    - Housing: Labor, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 30)
    - Housing: NYC, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 31)
    - Housing: Public, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 32)
    - Housing: State Laws, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 33)
    - Housing: Surveys, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 34)
    - Human Relations News, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 35)
    - Human Relations, Pennsylvania Commission on, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 36)
    - International Confederation of Free Trade Unions (ICFTU), 1962 (Box 339, Folder 37)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union (ILGWU) Hearings I, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 38)
    - ILGWU Hearings II, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 39)
    - International Union of Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers (IUE), 1962 (Box 339, Folder 40)
    - Israel, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 41)
    - Jacobs, Paul, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 42)
    - JLC: Birmingham, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 43)
    - JLC: Boston Monthly Reports, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 44)
    - JLC: Chicago, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 45)
    - JLC: Cleveland, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 46)
    - JLC: Connecticut, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 47)
    - JLC: Day-by-Day Activities, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 48)
    - JLC: Financial Reports, 1962 (Box 339, Folder 49)
    - JLC: Michigan, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 1)
    - JLC: Minnesota Monthly Report, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 2)
    - JLC Newsclips, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 3)
    - JLC: Philadelphia, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 4)
    - JLC: Philadelphia Monthly Reports, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 5)
    - JLC: Phoenix, AR, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 6)
    - JLC: Pittsburgh, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 7)
    - JLC: Rochester, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 8)
    - JLC: San Francisco, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 9)
    - JLC: Washington, DC, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Occupational Council, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 11)
    - Jewish War Veterans, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 12)
    - Labor and Civil Rights, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 13)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Conventions, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 14)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Discrimination in Unions, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 15)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Institutes, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 16)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: International Unions, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 17)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Local Unions, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 18)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Racism in Anti-Union Activity, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 19)
    - Labor and Civil Rights: Resolutions, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 20)
    - Labor Day Messages, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 21)
    - Large City Budgeting Committee, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 22)
    - Leadership Conference on Civil Rights, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 23)
    - League for Industrial Democracy, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 24)
    - Civil Service Employees Association (CSEA), Local 1707, American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees (AFCME), 1962 (Box 340, Folder 25)
    - Mass Media Committee, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 26)
    - Memos: Community Relations Councils, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 27)
    - Memos: Field Staff, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 28-29)
    - Memos: Interoffice, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 30)
    - Minnesota Freedom Walk, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 31)
    - Minnesota State Commission Against Discrimination, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 32)
    - Muravchik, Emanuel, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 33)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP), 1962 (Box 340, Folder 34)
    - National Association for the Advancement of Colored People (NAACP) and International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union (ILGWU), 1962 (Box 340, Folder 35)
    - National Association of Intergroup Relations Officials (NAIRO), 1962 (Box 340, Folder 36)
    - National Civil Liberties Clearing House, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 37)
    - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 38)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC), 1962 (Box 340, Folder 39-40)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Civil Liberties, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 41)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Civil Rights, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 42)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on the Community Relations Aspects of Development in the Middle East, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 43)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Committee on Interreligious Activities, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 44)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Executive Committee, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 45)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Immigration Committee, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 46)
    - National Community Relations Advisory Council (NCRAC): Joint Advisory Committee, 1962 (Box 340, Folder 47)